Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - Cataloged individually
        Arranged by box number.
        - Voices inside my head, Expression; SR-6984; Cekic, Began. (Box 7)
          BC Records
          Brooklyn, New York
        - Shooks; The rolla., 1996; SR-6987 (Box 7)
          Chronic
          England
        - Hummin', 1976; SR-7090 (Box 7)
          Lil' Man/Interscope Records
          Los Angeles, California
        - I feel like going on, 1980; SR-7091; Rance Allen Group. (Box 7)
          Stax: Distributed by Fantasy Records
          Berkeley, California
        - Unity (sing it, shout it)., 1970-1979; SR-7131 (Box 7)
          Kick Records
          Malibu, California
        - Beyond, 1980; SR-7265; Alpert, Herb. (Box 7)
          A&M Records
          Scarborough, Ontario
        - So unusual, 1984; SR-7266; Allison, George. (Box 7)
          Get Back
          Firenze, Italy
        - Luther's blues, 1974; SR-7267; Allison, Luther, 1939-1997. (Box 7)
          DJ copy; not for sale.
          Gold Plate Records
          United States
        - Fat comeback, 1999; SR-7268-7269; Alliance Ethnik (Musical group) (Box 7)
          Def Jam Recordings
          New York
        - Absurd, 1997; SR-7283; Fluke (Musical group) (Box 7)
          Virgin: Circa Records
        - Gateway., 1975; SR-7284; Abercrombie, John, 1944-2017 (Box 7)
          Eastbound Records
        - Things, 1982; SR-7285; Actuel (Musical group) (Box 7)
          Tiki Records
          Nashville, Tennessee
        - King without a crown, 1987; SR-7286; ABC (Musical group) (Box 7)
          Mercury Records
          Chicago, Illinois
        - Lexicon of love., 1982; SR-7287; ABC (Musical group) (Box 7)
          McDonald And Lydon Records
        - Just like in the movies., 1976; SR-7288 (Box 7)
          Atlantic Records
          New York, New York
        - Dirty deeds done dirt cheap., 1976; SR-7289; AC/DC (Musical group), (Box 7)
        - Love makes a woman, 1968; SR-7291; Acklin, Barbara. (Box 7)
          Brunswick Records
        - Brother Luck, 1981; SR-7292; SR-7551; ADC Band. (Box 7)
          Cotillion Records
        - Quero mais..., 1995; SR-7293; Ailton & Binho (Musical group) (Box 7)
          Afegan
          Brazil
        - Woke up this morning, 1997; SR-7294; A3 (Musical group) (Box 7)
          Promotional copy. White label. Original version from the Geffen cassette and compact disc, Exile on Cold Harbour Lane (GEFC/GEFD-25142).
          Geffen
        - Straight from the heart., 1978; SR-7295; Allen, Rance. (Box 7)
          Stax Records; Distributed by Fantasy Records
        - Love goes on, 1979; SR-7296 (Box 7)
          Sire Records
        - Strip, 1983; SR-7297; Ant, Adam. (Box 7)
          Epic
        - Prince Charming, 1981; SR-7298 (Box 7)
        - Addrisi Brothers., 1977; SR-7299 (Box 7)
          "Demonstration - not for sale"--Container.
          Buddah Records
        - Long stroke, 1978; SR-7300 (Box 7)
        - Talk that stuff, 1979; SR-7301; ADC Band. (Box 7)
        - Brother Luck, 1981; SR-7302; ADC Band. (Box 7)
        - Feel it, 1990; SR-7303; Afros (Musical group) (Box 7)
          Jive / Zomba
        - Ad vitam aeternam, 2001; SR-7304-7305; Afrodiziac (Musical group) (Box 7)
          Columbia
          France
        - Matinee, 1981; SR-7306; AfterBach (Musical group) (Box 7)
          American Recording Co.
        - Let's see what happens, 1990; SR-7307; Afro-Rican (Rap group) (Box 7)
          Promotional copy.
          Hilltak Records
        - Work it out; Gotta get my freak on, 1994; SR-7308; Afro-Rican (Rap group) (Box 7)
          Hip Hop Records
          Ft. Lauderdale, Florida
        - Gayle Adams., 1980; SR-7309 (Box 7)
          Pot Luck
          Nassau, Bahamas
        - Intercontinental, 1981; SR-7310; Afraid of Mice (Musical group) (Box 7)
          Charisma Records Ltd.
        - Juju music, 1982; SR-7311; Ade¿¿, Sunny. (Box 7)
          Mango: Island Records
        - Phantasy eyeland (what is your phantasy)., 1981; SR-7330 (Box 7)
          Sweet Mountain: Distributed by Sugar Hill Records
          Englewood, New Jersey
        - For those about to rock, 1981; SR-7333; AC/DC (Musical group) (Box 7)
        - Aaliyah., 2001; SR-7334-7335; Aaliyah, 1979-2001. (Box 7)
          Blackground
        - Antmusic; Don't be square (be there), 1980; SR-7336-7337; Adam and the Ants (Musical group) (Box 7)
          Promotional copy. Matrix / Runout (Label Side A): XSS 168533; Matrix / Runout (Label Side B): XSS 168534. "Special Version Of The Epic Lp: "Kings Of The Wild Frontier" JE 37033."
        - Blow up your video, 1988; SR-7338; AC/DC (Musical group) (Box 7)
          Atlantic: 81828-1 (on container spine: 7 81828-1).
        - Gayle Adams., 1980; SR-7339-7340 (Box 7)
          Prelude Records
        - Love fever, 1981; SR-7341; Adams, Gayle. (Box 7)
        - Feelgood, 1998; SR-7550; Rayce, Christopher. (Box 7)
          Swell
        - Flutes; Access code #1, 1997; SR-7092; Alpha (Musician) (Box 8)
          Matrix / Runout: HQ 007 A1 Matrix / Runout (Scratched Out): NIR 004 A1; Matrix / Runout: HQ 007 AA1 Matrix / Runout (Scratched Out): NIR 004 AA1.
          5HQ
        - Brasil-Brazil, 1988; SR-7263; Alves, Tania. (Box 8)
          T.C. Records; Distributed by Sutra Records
          Somerville, New Jersey
        - Brasil-Brazil, 1988; SR-7264; Alves, Tania. (Box 8)
        - Hideaway, 1976; SR-7270; America (Musical group) (Box 8)
          Warner Brothers Records
          Burbank, California
        - Apollonia., 1988; SR-7271 (Box 8)
          Promotional copy; white label.
        - Burning the ballroom down, 1978; SR-7272; Amazing Rhythm Aces. (Box 8)
          ABC Records
        - True spirit, 1994; SR-7273; Anderson, Californiarleen. (Box 8)
          Circa Records
        - Jam packed, 1987; SR-7274; Arrington, Steve. (Box 8)
          Mango Records
        - Jammin' national anthem, 1986; SR-7275; Arrington, Steve. (Box 8)
        - Positive power., 1984; SR-7276; Arrington, Steve. (Box 8)
          Atlantic 80127-1 (on container spine: 7 80127-1).
        - Happiness is--, 1990; SR-7277; Answered Questions (Musical group) (Box 8)
          Capitol Records
          Hollywood, California
        - Message from a soul sister, 1992; SR-7278; Anderson, Vicki. (Box 8)
          Faith & Hope Records
        - Soca savage, 1984; SR-7279; Arrow (Musician) (Box 8)
          Arrow; J & M One Stop Records distributor
          Barbados
        - Louis Armstrong meets Oscar Peterson, 1957; SR-7280; Armstrong, Louis, 1901-1971. (Box 8)
          Verve
          Paris, France
        - Send it, 1977; SR-7281; Ashford, Nickolas, (Box 8)
        - Stay free, 1979; SR-7282; Ashford & Simpson (Musical group) (Box 8)
        - Outubro, 1980; SR-7290; SR-7552; Azymuth (Musical group) (Box 8)
          Milestone
        - Bad luck, 1975; SR-7312; Atlanta Disco Band. (Box 8)
          Ariola America
          Beverly Hills, California
        - Visitors, 1977; SR-7313; Automatic Man (Musical group) (Box 8)
          Island Records
        - Playing with a different sex, 1981; SR-7314; Au Pairs (Musical group) (Box 8)
          Hubbub Records
          London, England
        - Little love, 1982; SR-7315-7316; Aurra (Musical group) (Box 8)
          Salsoul Records
        - Encore, 1978; SR-7317; Auger, Brian. (Box 8)
        - Happiness, heartaches, 1977; SR-7318; Oblivion Express (Musical group) (Box 8)
        - Every home should have one, 1981; SR-7319; Austin, Patti. (Box 8)
          Qwest Records
        - First strike, 1986; SR-7320; Atom Smashers (Musical group) (Box 8)
          Pathe¿¿ Marconi/EMI
        - Radiant, 1980; SR-7321; Atlantic Starr (Musical group), (Box 8)
        - All in the name of love, 1987; SR-7322; Atlantic Starr (Musical group) (Box 8)
          Warner Bros.: 1-25560 (on container: 25560-1).
        - Halim, 1997; SR-7323-7324; Atlas, Natacha. (Box 8)
          Beggars Banquet Records
        - Light as a feather, 1979; SR-7325; Azymuth (Musical group) (Box 8)
          Midsong International
        - No stranger to love., 1979; SR-7326; Ayers, Roy. (Box 8)
          Polydor Records
        - Salsa internacional 83, 1983; SR-7327; Azuquita y su Melao (Musical group) (Box 8)
          Matrix / Runout (Runout side A, etched): 160 815114 1 // 1 380 POLYGRAM; Matrix / Runout (Runout side B, etched): 160 815114 1 // 2 380 POLYGRAM.
        - Fever., 1979; SR-7328; Ayers, Roy. (Box 8)
        - Africa, center of the world, 1981; SR-7329; Ayers, Roy. (Box 8)
        - You might be surprised, 1985; SR-7332; Ayers, Roy. (Box 8)
          Columbia Records
        - How's everybody feelin'?, 1988; SR-7346-7347; B-Fats (Musician) (Box 8)
          Rooftops Records: Distributed by Profile Records
        - B & G Rhythm., 1978; SR-7353; B & G Rhythm (Musical group) (Box 8)
        - Ordinary man., 1979; SR-7358 (Box 8)
          Casablanca Record and FilmWorks
        - I want it that way, 1999; SR-7359-7360; Backstreet Boys. (Box 8)
          Jive
        - Free, 1998; SR-7364; Bacon Popper (Musical group) (Box 8)
          S.A.I.F.A.M./Megahit Records
          Lugagnano, VR, Italy
        - Still buggin', 1989; SR-7366; Bad Boy Orchestra. (Box 8)
          Tuff City: Smokin'
        - 'S easy Bach Gammon., 1977; SR-7380; Bach, Victor (Singer) (Box 8)
          Ariston
          Italy
        - Animal army., 1996; SR-7381; Babylon Zoo (Musical group) (Box 8)
          EMI
        - Baby Huey story: the living legend., 1971; SR-7383; Baby Huey, 1944-1970. (Box 8)
          CTI Records
        - Party mix, 1981; SR-7388-7389; B-52's (Musical group) (Box 8)
        - Whammy!, 1983; SR-7390-7391; B-52's (Musical group), (Box 8)
          Warner Bros. Records: 1-23819 (on container spine: 9 23819-1).
        - Music for teenage sex, 1981; SR-7585; Baby Buddha (Musical group) (Box 8)
          Portrait
        - You be you and I be me, 1988; SR-7036; Beatmaster Clay D. (Box 9)
          Vision Records
          Miami, Florida
        - Street music., 1981; SR-7062-7063 (Box 9)
          Sugarscoop
        - Caliente., 1976; SR-7076; Barbieri, Gato. (Box 9)
        - Mickey, 1982; SR-7142; Basil, Toni. (Box 9)
          Chrysalis Records
        - Bee Gees greatest, 1979; SR-7342-7343; Bee Gees, (Box 9)
          RSO Records
        - Sweeter than ever, 1986; SR-7344; Baron (Musician) (Box 9)
          B's Records
        - Chief inspector, 1986; SR-7345 (Box 9)
          Island Series; Distributed by Holborne Dist. Co. Ltd.
          Mount Albert, Onterio
        - 10th anniversary, 1985; SR-7348 (Box 9)
          Cocoa Records
        - Paradise in Gazankulu, 1988; SR-7352; Belafonte, Harry, 1927- (Box 9)
          Matrix / Runout: 7469711-A1; Matrix / Runout: 7469711-A1.
          EMI Manhattan
        - Just as I am., 1980; SR-7354 (Box 9)
        - Contagious, 1987; SR-7356-7357; Bar-Kays (Musical group) (Box 9)
          Mercury: 422 830 305-1 Q-1 (on container: 830 305-1 Q-1).
        - Echoes, 1984; SR-7361; Badarou, Wally. (Box 9)
        - Chinese wall, 1984; SR-7362; Bailey, Philip, 1951- (Box 9)
        - Uptown, 1971; SR-7363; Barnes, Gloria (Singer) (Box 9)
          "4-13-71"--Scratched on matrix.
          Manzie
          Kingston, Jamaica
        - Kollage, 1996; SR-7365; Bahamadia. (Box 9)
          Chrysalis: Manufactured by EMI Records
        - Jean Marie, 1986; SR-7367; Canta, Ballou. (Box 9)
          Bade Stars Music
        - Society don't let us down, 1996; SR-7368; Barons (Musical group) (Box 9)
          Fundamental
          Jamaica
        - Banging the wall, 1985; SR-7369; Bar-Kays (Musical group) (Box 9)
          Mercury; Manufactured and marketed by Polygram Records
        - Running alone., 1980; SR-7370 (Box 9)
        - Sue Barker., 1976; SR-7371; Barker, Sue (Singer) (Box 9)
          Cream Records
        - Heat of the wind., 1978; SR-7372; Bautista, Roland, 1951-2012. (Box 9)
        - Heart of the city, 1975; SR-7373; Barrabas (Musical group) (Box 9)
          Atco Records
        - Watch out, 1976; SR-7374; Barrabas (Musical group) (Box 9)
        - Star child., 1996; SR-7375; Bandoni, Mike. (Box 9)
          Monitor
        - Inside out, 1986; SR-7376; Bailey, Philip, 1951- (Box 9)
          Columbia: C 40209 (on container: FC 40209).
        - Lucio Battisti: songs., 1978; SR-7377-7378; Battisti, Lucio. (Box 9)
          RCA Records
          Germany
        - It takes two, 1988; SR-7379; Base, Rob. (Box 9)
          Profile
        - Rapture, 1986; SR-7382; Baker, Anita, 1958- (Box 9)
          Elektra Records
        - Piel de Barrabas, 1981; SR-7384; Barrabas (Musical group) (Box 9)
          Barclay
        - Young, gifted, and black, 1988; SR-7385-7386; Baron, Don. (Box 9)
          UNI Records
          Universal City, California
        - Give it to me, 1988; SR-7387; Bam Bam. (Box 9)
          Zyx Records
          Elbtal-Dorchheim, Germany
        - Banda Do Ze¿¿ Pretinho, 1978; SR-7392; Ben Jor, Jorge, 1945- (Box 9)
          Somlivre
          Rio de Janeiro
        - It's time you took another listen., 1977; SR-7396 (Box 9)
        - Odelay, 1996; SR-7397; Beck. (Box 9)
          Bong Load/Custom Records
        - Dam it., 1978; SR-7398 (Box 9)
          RCA Victor
        - Pullit all the way down, 1990; SR-7399; Beatmaster Clay D. (Box 9)
        - Creole girl., 1979; SR-7400; Ben Jor, Jorge, 1945- (Box 9)
          P&P Records
        - Mestizo, 1980; SR-7437; Bataan, Joe, 1942- (Box 9)
        - Basic Black., 1990; SR-7438; Basic Black (Musical group) (Box 9)
          Sound of New York: Motown
        - Instant joy, 1985; SR-7439; Baron (Musician) (Box 9)
        - Full of fire, 1986; SR-7440; Baron (Musician) (Box 9)
        - Turn me up, 1978; SR-7441; Barrow, Keith. (Box 9)
        - Dangerous, 1984; SR-7442; Bar-Kays (Musical group), (Box 9)
          Mercury: 422-818 478-1 M-1 (on container: 818 478-1 M-1).
        - Genuine liqua hits, 1995; SR-7444; Bakardy, Vell. (Box 9)
          Wild West Records: Marketed by American Recordings
        - As one., 1980; SR-7496 (Box 9)
        - Living eyes., 1981; SR-7497; Bee Gees. (Box 9)
        - Baby, won't you change your mind, 1972; SR-6952; Black Ivory (Musical group) (Box 10)
          Today Records
        - No time to burn., 1974; SR-6958 (Box 10)
        - Black sabbath, 1970; SR-6962; Black Sabbath (Musical group) (Box 10)
        - Take a ride, 1979; SR-7349; Wheeler, Beverly. (Box 10)
          Ariola Records
        - George Benson collection., 1981; SR-7350-7351; Benson, George, 1943- (Box 10)
          Warner
        - C'mon every beatbox; Badrock city; Beatboxes at dawn, 1986; SR-7355; Big Audio Dynamite (Musical group) (Box 10)
          "For promotion only."
        - Eleven it ends., 1981; SR-7393-7394 (Box 10)
          Takoma Records
        - While the city sleeps, 1986; SR-7395; Benson, George, 1943- (Box 10)
        - Funtaztik, 1981; SR-7401; Birdsong, Edwin. (Box 10)
        - Get up!, 1995; SR-7402; Bi-Nom (Musical group) (Box 10)
          DJ-promo
          Platinum Record Co.
        - Hog heaven, 1978; SR-7405; Bishop, Elvin. (Box 10)
          Capricorn Records
          Macon, Georgia
        - Cornbread, Earl and me original sound track recording., 1975; SR-7406; Byrd, Donald. (Box 10)
          Fantasy Records
        - Fix, 1997; SR-7407-7408; Blackstreet (Musical group) (Box 10)
          Interscope Records
          Santa Monica, California
        - Finally, 1999; SR-7409-7410; Blackstreet (Musical group) (Box 10)
          lifesong
        - Tomcattin', 1980; SR-7411-7412 (Box 10)
        - Black Sun., 1978; SR-7413; Black Sun (Musical group) (Box 10)
          Rockland Records
          Canada
        - Undiluted truth: (a blackman's leviathan), 1991; SR-7414; Black Radical MKII. (Box 10)
        - No reservations., 1975; SR-7415 (Box 10)
        - Walking downtown (Saturday night); Dance; White wind, 1976; SR-7416; Black Ivory (Musical group) (Box 10)
        - Beat on. Vol. 1: the best of the Blackbyrds, 1988; SR-7417; Blackbyrds (Musical group) (Box 10)
          BGP Records
        - Mary, 1999; SR-7418-7419; Blige, Mary J. (Box 10)
          Maryknoll
          Maryknoll, New York
        - Dinner with Raoul, 1978; SR-7420; Bliss Band. (Box 10)
        - Dub factor, 1983; SR-7421; Black Uhuru (Musical group) (Box 10)
          Malligator Records
        - I judge the funk, 1979; SR-7422; Black Ice (Musical group) (Box 10)
          White label; promotional copy.
          Harvest
        - No more drama, 2002; SR-7423-7424; Blige, Mary J. (Box 10)
          MCA Records
        - Lion goes from strength to strength, 1993; SR-7425-7426; Blade. (Box 10)
          691 Influential
        - Eat to the beat, 1979; SR-7427; Blondie (Musical group) (Box 10)
        - Back by popular demand, 1988; SR-7428; Blow, Kurtis. (Box 10)
        - America, 1985; SR-7429; Blow, Kurtis. (Box 10)
          Promotional copy.Mercury: 422-826 141-1 M-1 (on container: 826 141-1 M-1).
          Mercury; Distributed by Polygram
        - Kingdom Blow, 1986; SR-7430; Blow, Kurtis. (Box 10)
          Promotional copy
        - Electronic banana, 1984; SR-7431; Blowfly, 1939-2016. (Box 10)
          Oops! Records
        - Rappin', dancin', and laughin', 1980; SR-7432; Blowfly, 1939-2016. (Box 10)
          Weird World Records
          Hialeah, Florida
        - Fresh juice, 1983; SR-7433; Blowfly, 1939-2016. (Box 10)
          Omni
        - Live!, 1976; SR-7434-7435; Blue Magic (Musical group) (Box 10)
          WMOT Records
        - Blowfly's disco party, 1978; SR-7436; Blowfly, 1939-2016. (Box 10)
        - Made in America, 1980; SR-7445; Blues Brothers, (Box 10)
        - Welcome back, 1981; SR-7446; Blue Magic (Musical group) (Box 10)
        - Tobacco road; Why does it rain?, 1979; SR-7447-7448; Bob-A-Rela (Musical group) (Box 10)
          Channel
        - Me and Mr. Sanchez, 1981; SR-7449; Blue Rondo a la Turk (Musical group) (Box 10)
          Destiny Records
        - Best of Eddie Bo., 1997; SR-7463; Bo, Eddie. (Box 10)
          Hotrax Records
          Studio City, California
        - City life, 1985; SR-7507; Boogie Boys. (Box 10)
        - Funtaztik, 1981; SR-7600; Birdsong, Edwin. (Box 10)
        - Bob-a-Rella., 1979; SR-7601 (Box 10)
        - I wanna get down, 1980; SR-7633; Blast, C. L. (Box 10)
        - Won't let go., 1980; SR-7122; Brooklyn Dreams (Musical group) (Box 11)
        - Waiting on you, 1980; SR-7220-7221; Brick (Musical group) (Box 11)
          "For promotion only" Matrix / Runout (Side 1 Label): AL 36262 Matrix / Runout (Side 2 Label): BL 36262.
          Bang: Distributed by CBS Records
        - One step ahead, 1980; SR7450; Bohannon, Hamilton, (Box 11)
          Phase II Records
          Newmann, Georgia
        - Let's start II dance again, 1981; SR-7451-7452; Bohannon, Hamilton. (Box 11)
          Perception Records
        - Too hot to hold, 1979; SR-7453; Bohannon, Hamilton. (Box 11)
        - Alive, 1981; SR-7454; Bohannon, Hamilton, (Box 11)
          Newnan, Georgia
        - Here comes Bohannon, 1989; SR-7455; Bohannon, Hamilton. (Box 11)
        - Bohannon fever, 1982; SR-7456; Bohannon, Hamilton. (Box 11)
        - Feel like dancin'; The funk walk, 1980; SR-7457; Bohannon, Hamilton. (Box 11)
          Special promotional 12" disc.
        - Keep on dancing, 1974; SR-7458; Bohannon, Hamilton. (Box 11)
          D.E.T.T. Records
          Landover, Maryland
        - Zairo, 1983; SR-7459; Bobongo Stars (Musical group) (Box 11)
        - Hell of an act to follow., 1978; SR-7462 (Box 11)
        - Party up in here, 1979; SR-7466; Brides of Funkenstein (Musical group) (Box 11)